# **YURIY KOSHYK**

With 4+ years of experience, I combine design expertise and technical prowess to create impactful digital experiences focusing on business and user needs. Out of work I enjoy movies, books, play basketball and do street photography.

Stuttgart, Baden-Württemberg, DE

yuriykoshyk.com linkedin.com/in/yuriy-koshyk yuriy.koshyk@gmail.com +380974399377

## **WORK HISTORY**

#### **PRODUCT DESIGNER**

KOSH | Mar 2020 - Present

- Delivered 15+ projects, focusing on UX/UI design to drive business growth and user satisfaction;
- · Led full design research cycles, including user research, prototyping, and usability testing;
- · Translated business requirements and market insights into innovative design solutions;
- · Created high-performance digital products aligned with business metrics;
- · Monitored KPIs to optimise designs based on user feedback and data-driven insights.

#### **HEAD OF SYSTEMS & IT (CTO)**

DF Druckluft-Fachhandel GmbH | Aug 2023 - Jul 2024

- · Led the tech side of a multi-million dollar e-commerce company;
- Increased company revenue by 10% in 3 months with optimization of UX and system processes;
- · Effectively managed internal cross-functional team + 4 external partner companies;
- · Implemented the Agile methodology in the majority of the departments;
- · Successfully completed the company migration to Atlas Copco Group.

### **UX/UI DESIGNER & FRONTEND DEVELOPER**

Heimdal Data ApS | Dec 2022 - Jul 2023

- · Adhered to design standards and collaborate with stakeholders;
- · Developed user-friendly interfaces with a focus on user experience;
- · Wrote clean and scalable code that increased product performance;
- $\cdot\,$  Conduct user research and gather requirements for the design process;
- · Brought creative design trends and new technologies to the company's projects.

#### **PRINCIPLES**

Interaction Design

Visual Design

Design Systems

Prototyping

Material Design

Human-Centered Design

Heuristic evaluation

**Product Thinking** 

Usability Testing & A/B Testing

User Research

#### **TOOLS**

Figma, ProtoPie, Hotjar

Adobe Creative Suite, Blender

Google Analytics, PowerBI, SQL

HTML5, CSS3, SASS

JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Next.js

GSAP, Famer Motion, Tailwind

Webflow, Framer

#### **AWARDS**

Best Innovation and Creativity
Big Pitch Competition

### **EDUCATION**

PR) TR

UX Design Medium Projector Institute



Frontend Developer
IT School GolT



Media Communications Diploma

Bournemouth University International College



Humber College
Foundation in Computing

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

**EVENTPOS** [ Figma, Adobe Creative Suite ]

Role: Product Designer

Mobile payment solution specifically designed for events.

**<u>DF DRUCKLUFT-FACHHANDEL</u>** [ Agile, Azure, PowerBI, HTML, SASS, JS, SQL, Figma, Adobe CS ]

Role: Head of Systems & IT

Multi-million dollar e-commerce leader for complete compressed air solutions (a part of Atlas Copco Group).